novellshareware.com 2019-05-04

# NovellShareware.com, the Internet resource for novell, linux, windows, mac software

Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting Novell Shareware. We are committed to protecting the information about our visitors. This privacy policy states how we collect and use the information collected at our site. 

**What information do we collect?**

We gather certain information about you based upon your visit of our site. This information may include the Web site's Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") that you just came from, which URL you next go to, what browser you are using, and/or your Internet Protocol ("IP") address. The other collected data includes your operating system and its version, screen resolution, etc. These non-personal, technical characteristics are used to provide our visitors with the efficient service, to help them locate the necessary resources fast and convenient. What we also analyze is the search engine and search keywords use. This information is crucial to comply with search engine requirements and with our marketing strategies. 

We do not collect any personally identifiable information during your visit of our site. The personal information that we have available was submitted to us by the visitors knowingly. This happens in the following cases: 

   -   A person is placing an advertisement with our site under his/her personal name  
   -   A person is nominating him/herself to be a contact person  
   -   A person is sending us an inquiry about our site, services, opportunities to place an ad, etc. 

The following is related to personal information: name, address, telephone and fax numbers, e-mail, business contact details. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

We do not sell, share or barter the information about our visitors collected on the web site with the third parties. However, we may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. 

**Third-party advertising**

Novell Shareware offers advertising space for other companies. Among them our visitors will see Google Adsense advertising service on our site. The given service uses DART cookies to serve ads to the visitors. Please note that the information from the website contents, not from the users, is relevant for Google AdSense. DART cookies help to serve ads based on the users’ visit to the current site and to other sites on the Internet. A user may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting Google ads privacy policy, more info [here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

Other companies placing an ad within our site will also store cookies on your computer recording certain technical information about your visits. No personally identifiable information is made available in this case. 

**Disclaimer**

All the information published in the catalog as the software description is the sole responsibility of a person/organization making a posting of a corresponding product. Please send all your requests, questions or claims to the author of the corresponding posting, not to the staff of Novell Shareware. 

**Data security**

This document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. Other sites accessible through our site have their own privacy policies and data collection, use, and disclosure practices. Please consult each site's privacy policy. We are not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties. 

**Privacy contact**

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.
